<CHANGES>
## 2026.05.24.03
- **Fix: Antigravity CLI sessions displayed corrupted terminal output on first launch.** Go's internal log messages were being written directly to the terminal, overlapping with the agent's own display. The log directory the agent uses to redirect those messages away from the screen now exists before the agent starts.
- **Fix: Agent could fail on first launch with an authentication error after a full sync to persistent storage** (complete fix — v2026.05.24.02 contained the right logic but an unrelated packaging issue meant the fix was not installed on upgrade; this release ensures it lands correctly).

## 2026.05.24.02
- **Fix: Agent could fail on first launch with an authentication error after a full sync to persistent storage.** After a clean complete bake, the post-sync cleanup routine was inadvertently removing the overlay's working directory from the filesystem. The overlay appeared mounted and reads worked fine, but all writes — including the OAuth token refresh that runs at every startup — returned "No such file or directory", causing agents to report auth errors or loop on launch. Fixed.

## 2026.05.24.01
- **Fix (data loss — important): the proper fix for agents forgetting your sessions.** v2026.05.18.08 announced a fix for this — that release tackled one symptom but missed the underlying cause. Your agent (Copilot, OpenCode, Codex, Kilo Code, Goose) could still occasionally start as if it had never seen you before, or hang on the "Waking..." loading screen. This release fixes the underlying behaviour. **Already-lost session history is not recoverable by upgrading.** If an agent now hangs at Waking or complains about a corrupted database, in the affected agent's directory (e.g. `~/.codex/`, `~/.copilot/`) delete any `.db-shm` or `.db-wal` files that don't have a matching `.db` next to them, then re-launch — the agent starts fresh.
- **Fix: Agent commands no longer occasionally fail mid-storage-save.** On busy servers, a command running in the brief window when the plugin was saving RAM to persistent storage could fail with "No such file or directory" — most reproducible on a clean Antigravity install. The save and the launch no longer collide.
- **Security: Tighter checks on agent installs.** Downloaded agent packages are now signature-verified before being unpacked, and downloads must use HTTPS. Defence-in-depth — nothing observable in normal use.
- **Improve: Tidier cleanup when an install fails.** A failed agent install no longer leaves behind hidden host resources, so the host stays clean across many transient failures.

## 2026.05.23.19
- **Feat: Antigravity CLI added.** Google's coding assistant is now in the Agent Store. Tracks upstream versions for the update card, and supports Resume from a specific conversation or the most recent.
- **Feat: Keep-a-copy on upgrade.** Optionally retain a per-version backup of an agent's layers when upgrading. The version picker grows a "Restore" option listing the kept backups; pick one to roll back to that version. The upgrade dialog shows disk usage up-front so you can decide whether to keep a copy. Backups live alongside the active layers in your configured persistence path.
- **Feat: Native keyring for agents that ask for one.** Agents that store their auth tokens in a system keyring previously re-prompted for auth every session because Unraid has no keyring daemon. The plugin now starts a per-user keyring at agent launch, so the token survives across sessions. Today this benefits Antigravity CLI; the framework is generic.
- **Feat: Agent CLIs work from the Unraid host terminal after a reboot.** Running an agent CLI from the standard Unraid Terminal button right after a reboot previously failed with "No such file or directory" — agent storage was only attached on demand when the plugin's own webterm opened. The plugin now attaches every installed agent at array start, so the binaries are available to any shell on the host immediately.
- **Fix: Setting "Terminal User" to a non-root account now works end-to-end.** Previously the Settings dropdown saved the wrong value, the agent's home was effectively read-only, terminals failed to launch, and the Store-card panels kept showing the previous user's data after the switch. All four issues are fixed, and the Settings page auto-reloads on user-switch so per-user data re-renders against the new home. All close, agent-upgrade, hard-stop, plugin-stop, plugin-uninstall, and array-stop paths now reach non-root sessions too.
- **Fix: "Terminal session not found" after a busy server tick.** Other processes on the host can occasionally leave the shared tmux socket directory with permissions tmux rejects, and every plugin terminal would then fail to start. The plugin now uses its own private socket directory, isolated from anything else on the box.
- **Fix: Agent-upgrade "open sessions" count no longer inflated by orphan terminals.** Failed launches and unclean exits previously left terminal-server processes alive forever. The upgrade-confirm dialog counted these as live sessions, inflating the warning. The plugin now reconciles terminal-server processes against running sessions on every list and array-start, and reaps orphans automatically.
- **Fix: Resume button now appears for Antigravity CLI workspaces after close + re-add.** The close-time resume-id capture wasn't aware of agy's specific exit behaviour or where it stores its conversation files; both handled now. Note: agy itself still requires two Ctrl-Ds to exit — that's upstream behaviour, not something the plugin can change.
- **Fix: Claude Resume cross-workspace contamination.** Closing workspace B sometimes saved workspace A's session id, so clicking Resume on B later opened Claude with the wrong session and refused with "No conversation found". Resume-id discovery is now scoped to the closing workspace.
- **Fix: CLI Args panel reflects the active Terminal User.** After switching the Terminal User in Settings, the per-agent Args panel kept showing the previous user's saved arg until the page was hard-refreshed. The Settings page now auto-reloads on a user-switch.
- **Improve: Release-notes link + A-Z sort on the Agent Store.** Each Store card now shows a Release-notes link when the agent's source publishes a changelog URL. The agent grid gets an A-Z/Z-A toggle, persisted in the URL.

## 2026.05.18.08
- **Fix (data loss — important): your agents stop forgetting your sessions.** A long-standing bug in how the plugin saves data from RAM to your Flash drive could silently drop the session-history database files used by Codex CLI, GitHub Copilot, Kilo Code, OpenCode and Goose — so an agent would occasionally start as if it had never seen you before, or hang on the "Waking Codex CLI..." loading screen. In severe cases the whole Unraid dashboard could freeze for minutes when the plugin was in use (downstream effect of an agent stuck reading a half-deleted database). This release fixes the save routine and adds defence-in-depth checks. **Already-lost session history is not recoverable by upgrading.** If an agent now hangs at Waking or complains about a corrupted database, in the affected agent's directory (e.g. `~/.codex/`, `~/.copilot/`) delete any `.db-shm` or `.db-wal` files that don't have a matching `.db` next to them, then re-launch — the agent starts fresh.
- **Improve: Plugin upgrades no longer interrupt your work.** Routine upgrades from this release forward leave your terminal sessions running and your agents in place — typical upgrade time drops from ~30–90s of session-killing teardown to ~5–15s. The longer path is still used (and the release notes will say so) when a release genuinely needs to rebuild your storage layout. **One-time exception:** the upgrade FROM the previous storefront TO this release will still take the long path, because this release introduces the marker the plugin uses to recognise compatible layouts. From the next upgrade onward, routine updates run uninterrupted. Unsaved RAM data is flushed to Flash just before the swap, so a sudden power loss during the brief upgrade window doesn't lose recent activity.
- **Improve: Qwen Code's DashScope API key now appears as a labelled password field on the agent's Store card** — previously users had to discover the `DASHSCOPE_API_KEY` env variable name themselves from the qwen-code README. Alternative providers (Ollama, vLLM, …) can still be configured via the general env panel.

## 2026.05.18.05
- Fix (data loss): Storage consolidation no longer deletes the `.gemini/tmp/` directory during its pre-bake prune. That path holds gemini-cli's per-project session chat logs (`.gemini/tmp/<projectId>/chats/session-*.jsonl`) — durable user state, not cache. The previous behaviour was silently wiping chat history on every consolidate, and crashing the next gemini launch with an ENOENT on the session log. If you've used gemini-cli with this plugin before this release, past chat history is unfortunately not recoverable; from this release forward, it persists. (Verified on the test box: a synthetic chat log survives a full consolidate with content intact.)
- Fix: Workspace session resume now works correctly for Kilo Code, Pi Coder, GitHub Copilot, and Goose. The resume flags wired into the "attach to existing session" command had drifted from each agent's current upstream CLI:
  - Kilo Code: `resume_latest` now passes `--continue` (previously plain `{binary} {args}`, which started a new session). Per-ID resume uses `--session <id>` (canonical form of `-s`).
  - Pi Coder: `resume_latest` now uses `--continue` (previously `--resume`, which opens an interactive picker that hangs in the SSH-attach flow with no TTY input). Per-ID resume uses `--session <id>`.
  - GitHub Copilot CLI: `resume_latest` now uses `--continue` (previously plain `{binary} {args}`). Per-ID resume keeps `--resume=<id>`.
  - Goose: per-ID resume now uses `session --resume -n <id>` (previously `session --name <id>`, which CREATED a new session named `<id>` instead of resuming an existing one).
- Fix: OpenCode is detected as installed reliably. The plugin's installed-state check was looking at `bin/opencode`, but the npm package ships `bin/opencode.exe` (a cross-platform naming convention also used by Claude Code — the postinstall replaces the file with the platform-matched binary). The agent worked anyway via the resolved `node_modules/.bin/opencode` symlink, but the inconsistency could surface as "INSTALL" reappearing on the Store card under some refresh paths.

## 2026.05.18.02
- Improve: Storage consolidation no longer trips on busy workspaces. When the boot integrity / auto-consolidation pass runs while a workspace has files open on the home mount, the plugin now defers the operation (with a clear "deferred — busy" log) instead of marking it a failure and counting it against the auto-halt threshold. The Storage tab also gains a small non-blocking banner if a real consolidate failure happens, so it surfaces at the first occurrence rather than only after the supervisor escalates to a halt. When a failure does happen, the last 50 lines of the debug log are now snapshotted to `/boot/config/plugins/unraid-aicliagents/failures/` and the stderr tail is inlined into the lifecycle log entry, so the cause survives `/tmp` rotation between the failure and the next time anyone looks.
- Fix: Agent channel selections (and other Settings writes that go through the atomic writer) reliably persist across a page reload on heavily-loaded servers. The atomic-write path now disables the userland buffer and fsyncs before the rename, closing a cross-process visibility lag that occasionally made the beta-channel radio appear unchecked immediately after saving.

## 2026.05.17.02
- Improve: Out of beta. The plugin now ships as a regular Community Applications release — the Beta flag in the CA template has been removed.
- Fix: Codex CLI launches correctly after install. From `@openai/codex` v0.99, OpenAI split the native binary into a per-platform optional dependency, so the previous expected binary path was wrong and Codex crashed immediately with "Agent Binary Missing". The path is now correct, and a fallback preserves pre-v0.99 installs that haven't been reinstalled.
- Improve: Agent-storage halts now self-heal silently. If the boot integrity check finds an agent's binary layers missing, the plugin automatically re-runs the install (agent storage is just npm code — there's nothing to lose) instead of presenting a scary "Storage Unavailable — start fresh and abandon data" prompt. Real user-data halts (home storage) keep their destructive confirmation, but the WIPE dialog now actually has an input box (previously the gate was decorative, and Cancel looped back to the same overlay with no escape). Every halt card also gains a Retry-integrity-check button and a Dismiss-for-24h button, so the destructive path is never the only escape.
- Improve: Halt overlay follows the active Unraid theme (light / dark / auto) instead of forcing a dark+orange palette that didn't blend with the rest of the UI.
- Fix: Uninstalling an agent now cleans up its layer-manifest entry and clears any pending halt sentinel. Without this, the next reboot's integrity sweep treated the just-uninstalled agent as "all expected layers missing" and surfaced a phantom Storage Unavailable halt for an agent that wasn't even on disk anymore.

## 2026.05.15.16
- Feat: Connect to workspace terminals from your local SSH client. A new "SSH Keys" card in Settings registers a public key for tmux-attach access; clicking the key icon on any workspace row copies a ready-to-paste `ssh user@host -t "tmux attach …"` command (UTF-8 locale prefixed so agent status glyphs render correctly). Recommended on Windows: Windows Terminal, not the legacy "Windows PowerShell" host. A key registered in one browser is recognised across every browser pointed at the same Unraid box.
- Fix: Agent Marketplace no longer shows "No agents match the current filter" while matching cards are visible above (an empty-state race during the initial grid render).
- Fix: SSH Key Setup modal renders cleanly on Unraid 7.2.x — the close button, OS tabs, and command-copy buttons no longer appear as orange-bordered rectangles.
- Improve: "Saving session to Flash drive" overlay and the workspace Secrets card now say "persistent storage" — clearer wording that doesn't expose where the data physically lives.

## 2026.05.12.06
- Fix: Upgrading an agent no longer occasionally fails with "Install Failed (Bake Error)". Two storage-bakes of the same agent could race during an upgrade (one finishing its remount while the other was mid-bake); a per-agent lock now serializes them, and a redundant duplicate bake on agent install was removed.

## 2026.05.12.05
- Improve: Reduced Flash-drive (USB stick) write wear. The storage layer now syncs to Flash on a gentler cadence (a ~2-hour default window instead of 30 minutes), consolidates its SquashFS layers far less often, and no longer writes regenerable agent caches to Flash at all — the npm cache, `~/.cache`, agent temp/telemetry directories, etc. are excluded from the bake. Net effect: the plugin writes a lot less to your USB stick. Storage that's currently carrying that cache cruft is slimmed down automatically on the next layer consolidation. (Migrated/backup data is never touched by this — clear that via the storage tab's recovery card if you want it gone.)

## 2026.05.12.02
- Fix: Upgrading an agent while one of its workspace sessions is open no longer strands that session. Some agents (e.g. Claude Code 2.1.x) have replaced their legacy "cli.js" entry point with a native binary; the launch now re-checks the agent's binary on every relaunch rather than using the path resolved when the session was opened, so an in-place upgrade is picked up automatically. (If a session was already stranded by such an upgrade, close and reopen that workspace once and it will pick up the new binary.)
- Improve: After a plugin install or upgrade, the agent Store cards now show each uninstalled agent's available version straight away — a background version-cache refresh runs on install, so you no longer have to press "Check for Updates" first.

## 2026.05.12.01
- Feat: Environment & secrets management. Every agent's Store card and every workspace now has an "Environment" panel covering general env vars AND API keys/secrets, with full add / edit / delete for both. Secrets are masked and stored separately under tightened (0600) permissions; general vars are managed more loosely. Per-workspace values override the per-agent defaults, and values apply automatically to newly opened terminal sessions ("hot-apply") with no workspace rebuild. Agents that ship default env vars seed them on install as an editable starting set. Replaces the old hardcoded-only API-key vault (the Config-tab "Secrets Vault" card is removed); clearing a value via the UI now actually clears it.
- Feat: Per-agent and per-workspace CLI arguments. A new "Args" panel on each Store card sets default extra flags for that agent (e.g. --max-turns 5), and a workspace can override them in its drawer. Arguments are validated against shell metacharacters. Changing args while a session is open offers "Apply now" — the agent is reloaded in place (Ctrl-C + relaunch) with the new flags, no destroy/recreate.
- Feat: Auto-launch workspaces. A per-workspace toggle in the Terminal panel marks a workspace to start its session automatically — on page load, and after an agent install or upgrade — so your usual workspaces come back without clicking through.
- Feat: Agent Store cards redesigned. Each agent is now one card with five progressive-disclosure panels: Channel, Environment/Secrets, Runtime (RAM, storage stats), Terminal (tmux), and Storage. tmux settings have four tiers of precedence — built-in then agent default then workspace override then a .conf escape hatch — with only divergent keys persisted. Per-agent secret schemas can carry multiple fields (Goose, for instance, registers Provider / Model / provider keys).
- Feat: Two new agents — Goose (Block) and Qwen Code — plus a new agent-source framework so the plugin can manage tools that aren't published to npm (GitHub-release binaries, curl-installers, tarballs), not just npm packages.
- Feat: Workspace resume. Closing a workspace from the drawer now captures the agent's resume id — a printed UUID, a named session, or, for agents like OpenCode that print nothing, the most recent id from their own session database — and offers a "Resume" button next to "Start Fresh" the next time you open a session on that path. Wide tmux capture plus retries so long resume lines aren't truncated.
- Feat: Graceful agent upgrades. Installing or upgrading an agent now enumerates and cleanly closes the active workspace sessions for that agent first (preserving each session's resume id) before swapping the binary, instead of yanking it out from under running terminals. The install/upgrade button warns you with the list of sessions that will be closed; the New Workspace overlay greys out agents whose install is in progress; the install-progress panel appears immediately on click.
- Feat: Cold-start loading overlay. The terminal shows a spinner, the agent icon and a "Starting [agent]..." message for the whole cold-start window (most of which is the agent's own startup) instead of a blank terminal, dismissing as soon as the agent produces output.
- Improve: Storage robustness overhaul. A background storage daemon now owns all SquashFS bake/consolidate work, so the UI never blocks on storage I/O and the "syncing..." indicator clears reliably (it polls real state instead of guessing on a timer). Every layer write is atomic and checksum-verified. On boot your persisted layers are integrity-checked: corruption, missing layers, or a path/host mismatch is detected, you're notified, workspace access is held until it's resolved, and — where a copy survives in a backup/migrated sibling directory — a one-click "Restore" rebuilds from it. Un-baked data is monitored with graduated thresholds. Fixed a class of silent data loss where resume ids, workspace records or agent credentials written during a consolidation cycle could be discarded when the in-memory layer was wiped after the bake. Auto-consolidation now defers while the terminal is busy and runs when idle, so deltas no longer pile up indefinitely on the home stack. Writes to the Flash drive — API keys, plugin config, layer manifests — are forced to disk on every change so they survive an abrupt reboot instead of lingering in the OS page cache. The old per-user sync daemon is retired.
- Fix: ZRAM storage initialisation now works on Unraid 7.2.x and other kernels where zram is built in — a capability probe (/sys/class/zram-control, /dev/zram0) replaces the fatal modprobe zram, with an mkfs.xfs fallback when mkfs.ext4-on-block-device isn't available. Resolves the install failure reported in GitHub issue #5.
- Fix: Agent version display. The Plugins "Update" card and the Store-card version badge showed v0.0.0 / "v?" for most installed agents on a fresh boot, because version discovery was reading package.json from an overlay that wasn't mounted yet. It now mounts on demand and reads the real semver, and a one-shot backfill repairs the registry on upgrade. The version picker also now filters pre-release tags out of the Stable channel correctly and reliably installs the version you pick — downgrade, reinstall and pick-specific-version were no-ops on the redesigned cards.
- Fix: Persistence paths on custom Unraid pools (ZFS pools, user-named cache pools) are accepted instead of rejected with a misleading "outside allowed prefixes" error; stopping the array is no longer blocked by terminals holding a working directory under /mnt/user (the array-stop event is handled, not just full shutdown); installed agents resolve on the main Unraid shell and web terminal (goose, qwen etc. wrappers in /usr/local/bin, and the workspace terminal PATH includes every installed agent's bin directory).
- Fix: UI polish — web fonts now load (the @import was mid-stylesheet, which browsers silently drop); Chrome no longer autofills the agent search box with "root" and hides every card; the "Leave site?" dialog no longer pops when navigating away from the terminal tab; the Plugins page now shows the support-thread link and a plugin description.
- Fix: Per-agent launch reliability — Claude Code's native binary layout, Codex-CLI's vendored Rust binary, OpenCode's cache-directory creation, Goose's first-run TUI prompt, Qwen Code's binary path, and fast-exit handling so a mis-configured agent shows its error instead of relaunch-looping; Node and npm caches are kept on tmpfs and never written to the Flash drive; broadened post-install cleanup of stale /tmp artifacts; XML-escaping fixes in the installer/uninstaller hooks.

## 2026.04.16.27
- Fix: Migration script wrote home sqsh to agent_storage_path instead of home_storage_path. When paths differ (common for users with persistence_base configured), the home sqsh was placed where only agents are expected, causing mount failure. Now reads home_storage_path and persistence_base from config separately. Also searches all relevant paths for legacy IMG files and raw folders.

## 2026.04.16.26
- Fix: Background migration hung the installer UI. The nohup backgrounded process kept file descriptors open, preventing the PLG install script from exiting. Added disown after the background launch to fully detach the migration process from the installer shell.

## 2026.04.16.25
- Fix: Removed test-harness.sh download from PLG. The dev test script was excluded from the public GitHub repo but still referenced as a FILE download in the PLG, causing install failure on production servers pulling from GitHub.

## 2026.04.16.24 - The "Storage Intelligence" Update
- Feat: SquashFS Storage Architecture - Replaced Btrfs loopback images with a layered SquashFS + ZRAM overlay system. Agent binaries and home directories now use compressed read-only layers with a RAM write buffer, dramatically reducing Flash USB wear while maintaining instant persistence. Automatic layer consolidation keeps storage footprint minimal.
- Feat: Array-Aware Storage - The plugin now detects when configured storage paths depend on the Unraid array or pools. When the array is stopped, a Storage Unavailable overlay guides users through emergency options. When the array starts, the plugin automatically restores normal operation with no manual intervention needed.
- Feat: Emergency Mode - When all storage is on the stopped array, users can install a temporary AI agent directly into RAM and launch an emergency terminal session. OpenCode is recommended as it requires no authentication. Temporary agents and sessions are automatically cleaned up when the array restarts.
- Feat: Agent Version Management - Replaced the simple Stable/Preview toggle with a full version picker dropdown per agent. Browse all available versions with tagged releases and stable versions within a configurable time window. Supports upgrade, downgrade, and channel selection (latest, next, beta, etc). Update notifications appear via Unraid built-in notification system on a configurable schedule.
- Feat: Configurable Storage Locations - Home and agent storage paths can now be independently configured and migrated between Flash, array shares, cache pools, and unassigned devices. A guided migration flow persists data, copies files with progress tracking, and consolidates at the destination.
- Feat: Array Stop Warning - When stopping the array, a warning dialog lists affected AI sessions and storage paths. Users can choose to proceed (sessions are terminated gracefully) or cancel. Sessions on non-array paths continue running uninterrupted.
- Feat: Docker Tool Wrappers - Integrated proxy scripts for Docker-based tools (e.g. semgrep). When an agent requests a tool, it transparently runs via Docker container with clear install instructions if the image is not available.
- Improve: Settings Page Performance - The Agent Store tab no longer blocks on npm registry queries during page load. Version data is cached and refreshed in the background, making the settings page load instantly.
- Improve: Install Progress Resilience - Agent install and update progress bars now survive page refreshes. If you navigate away and return during an installation, the progress bar resumes from where it left off.
- Improve: Storage Migration Safety - Consolidation is skipped when source or target is on Flash USB to avoid unnecessary write amplification. Config file writes are serialized to prevent corruption from concurrent operations.
- Improve: Real-Time Status Updates - Storage status changes (array start/stop) are detected via Nchan for instant UI updates, with a polling fallback for reliability. Page reloads no longer trigger the browser unsaved changes dialog.
- Fix: Terminal clipboard and right-click behavior restored to browser defaults.
- Fix: Storage path availability detection now correctly identifies when array shares are inaccessible.
- Fix: Home storage path setting now correctly applies to home operations.

## 2026.04.06.54
- Feat: Full-Screen Terminal Overlay - Added a dedicated 'Temporary Terminal' accessible directly from the agent drawer. This provides a blur-backed, full-screen bash session synchronized with your active workspace directory for manual CLI operations.
- Feat: Ready-Now Workspace Performance - Implemented 'Boot-time Resurrection' which proactively pre-loads all AI agent binaries and user home RAM volumes during system startup or installation. This eliminates the restoration delay previously encountered on first use.
- Improve: Terminal-to-Workspace Synchronization - Switching between workspace tabs now automatically reloads all terminal sessions (both overlay and tab-based) to ensure the path always matches the visible project.
- Improve: Btrfs Storage Resilience - Hardened the agent storage lifecycle with mandatory auto-mounting and namespace verification, ensuring reliable binary availability even after unexpected system reboots.
- Improve: UI Initialization Feedback - Added a descriptive 'Restoring Home Storage' overlay to the terminal interface to provide users with visual status during the first background restoration of persistent data to RAM.
- Fix: Loopback Image Stability - Optimized the Btrfs storage floor and headroom constraints to prevent 'No space left' (ENOSPC) errors during image resizing, and ensured storage locks are correctly enforced after maintenance cycles.

## 2026.04.04.05
- Improve: Storage Intelligence - Implemented advanced Btrfs management including tail-block evacuation for reliable image shrinking, intelligent expansion guards to protect Flash drive headroom, and automated self-healing for corrupted loopback images.
- Improve: UI & UX Refinement - Redesigned the Agent Store and configuration drawers with a high-density layout, improved spacing, and automated drawer management for a smoother workspace transition.
- Improve: Terminal Resilience - Significantly hardened terminal session stability and connection reliability through improved user isolation and robust environment variable propagation.
- Improve: Diagnostics & Transparency - Enhanced the storage dashboard with "Truthful Capacity Reporting" showing both logical data size and physical disk footprint, along with better error visibility for system maintenance tasks.
- Fix: Storage Permissions - Resolved edge cases where agent storage could become write-protected or inaccessible due to kernel-level loopback locks.

## 2026.03.28.05
- Improve: Data Integrity - Implemented SQLite 'Surgical Repair' (PRAGMA integrity_check) and automated pre-flight recovery for OpenCode and Claude agent databases.
- Improve: Performance - Drastically reduced plugin upgrade time and periodic sync latency on USB Flash drives by implementing '--size-only' rsync and excluding non-essential caches (.npm, .bun).
- Security: Replaced 'eval' command execution with safe Bash array-based execution in the terminal wrapper to eliminate arbitrary code execution risks.
- Fix: PHP 8.0+ Compatibility - Resolved 'unlink' warnings and improved custom error handling to correctly respect the suppression operator (@).
- Fix: Upgrade Reliability - Added automated RAM-to-Flash backup and SQLite 'wal_checkpoint' during plugin updates to ensure zero data loss.

## 2026.03.27.20
- Fix: Critical XML Validation (Escapes raw ampersands in changelogs to resolve 'XML parse error' failures).
- Fix: Switched to high-fidelity literal replacement logic for public releases to prevent corrupted .plg structure.

## 2026.03.27.19
- Feat: Added Shell Integration aliases for all agents (kilo, pi, codex, droid, nanocoder).
- Fix: Resolved 'Status not available' by fixing GitHub URL extraction for SSH-over-443 remotes.
- Fix: Corrected changelog replacement to prevent symbol corruption during publishing.

## 2026.03.27.18
- Feat: Added Support for OpenCode, Claude Code, and NanoCoder agents.
- Feat: Global Shell Integration providing native 'claude', 'gemini', and 'opencode' aliases in all SSH and local terminal sessions.
- Feat: Integrated "User & Architecture Guide" links within the Settings page and Terminal Drawer for instant help access.
- Improve: Terminal Stability with optimized shell environment propagation and automated SQLite self-healing for agent history.
- Fix: Reinforced recursive permission enforcement for agent binaries to prevent 'Permission denied' / EACCES errors in RAM.

## 2026.03.18.01
- Feat: Added Factory CLI (@factory/cli) support
- Feat: Integrated 'droid' binary and Factory session management
- UI: Added Factory icon and updated agent registry

## 2026.03.17.35 - The "Professional Workspace" Update
- Feat: Advanced Workspace Environment Management - New "Manage ENV" drawer overlay allows viewing and overriding global API keys per workspace without affecting global settings.
- Feat: Intelligent API Persistence - Dynamically discovers and persists API keys for all installed agents (OpenCode, Kilo Code, etc.) in the Secrets Vault.
- Feat: Hybrid Home Persistence - Implemented a decoupled background sync daemon that asynchronously mirrors the high-performance RAM home directory to the Flash drive.
- Feat: Multi-User Migration - Seamlessly migrates AI agent data when switching the active Unraid user, ensuring chat history is preserved.
- Improve: Premium UI Theming - Unified orange button theme, consistent card layouts, and professional blue-sidebar help styling throughout the manager.
- Improve: Performance & Stability - Optimized terminal initialization to eliminate 502 Bad Gateway errors and implemented atomic locking for background sync operations.
- Improve: Clipboard Synchronization - Enabled OSC 52 support for dual-direction clipboard synchronization between the AI terminal and your browser.
- Improve: TrueColor Support - Full 24-bit TrueColor environment propagation across the entire terminal stack for better syntax highlighting.
- Fix: Terminal Rendering - Resolved scrolling and corruption issues in terminal sessions, particularly for limited-user contexts.
- Fix: Setting Persistence - Ensured fallback API keys and backup schedule settings correctly persist between reboots and user changes.
- Fix: Environment Visibility - Resolved a critical bug where custom environment variables and Secrets Vault keys were not correctly propagated to the active AI agent.

## 2026.03.09.19 - The "Premium UX" Update
- Feat: Expanded Agent Store - Added support for Claude Code, OpenCode, Kilo Code, Pi Coder, and Codex CLI.
- Feat: Integrated Node.js Environment - Bundled Node.js (v22.22.0) with npm for seamless, portable agent management.
- Feat: Premium Uninstaller UI - Completely redesigned uninstallation with quiet logging and a resilient, high-contrast summary box confirming preservation of settings and chats.
- Feat: Premium Installer UX - Polished installation flow with professional status updates and a new "INSTALL COMPLETE" visual summary.
- Improve: System Branding - Unified all system notifications and UI elements under the "AI CLI Agents Plugin" title.
- Improve: Boot Resiliency - Implemented persistent USB source caching for instant UI availability on reboot.
- Improve: Hardware Optimization - Moved all runtime logs to RAM (/tmp) to minimize USB flash drive wear.
</CHANGES>
