<CHANGES>
## v2026.03.02.17

- **Metadata Overlay**: Hover over any workspace tab to see its full filesystem path and active Gemini Session ID.
- **Session Reset**: Added a manual "RESET" button to the tab overlay to clear stuck sessions or start fresh conversations.
- **Smart Workspace Isolation**: Robust project detection that ensures nested folders correctly maintain their own independent Gemini sessions.
- **Reliable Session Resumption**: Significant improvements to session recovery across server reboots and browser refreshes.
- **Cleaner Tab Labels**: Redesigned tab titles that prioritize the workspace folder name and ONLY show status emojis (◇, ✦, ✋) when active.
- **Polished Terminal UI**: Added a balanced 8px padding around the terminal with rounded corners and transparent background for better theme integration.
- **Eliminated Scrollbars**: Implemented persistent suppression of internal and external scrollbars for a cleaner, full-screen terminal experience.
- **Dependency Upgrades**: Upgraded to the latest stable versions of Gemini CLI (v0.31.0), Node.js (v22.22.0 LTS), and tmux (v3.6a).
- **Improved Security**: Added CSRF validation for all state-changing AJAX actions.

### v2026.02.27.20 - Initial Release: Key Features

- **Native AI Integration**: Direct integration of Google Gemini into the Unraid WebUI, providing a powerful AI agent for server management and coding tasks.
- **Multi-Workspace Terminal**: Support for multiple terminal sessions (Workspaces). Open different folders in separate tabs to manage various projects simultaneously.
- **Dynamic Status Tracking**: Tabs poll terminal state in real-time, displaying Gemini's status icons (Ready ◇, Working ✦, Action Required ✋) and active task descriptions.
- **Integrated File Browser**: Seamlessly navigate your server's filesystem to select and open new workspaces.
- **Responsive Terminal Design**: A modern, high-performance terminal wrapper with dynamic resizing that automatically fills available screen space and fits perfectly above the footer.
- **Unraid Theme Integration**: Harmonious UI design that matches your Unraid theme (Light/Dark) and respects standard system variables.
- **Smart Session Management**: Persistent terminal sessions that remain active in the background, allowing you to switch between tasks without losing state.
</CHANGES>
